Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series III. Research and Consulting
  - Clarence Stein research files
    - Stockholm Suburbs, Stein Notes (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Swedish Town Planning (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - "Rus in Urb: A prologue to the Evaluation of the Impact of the Radburn Idea on Modern Town Planning" Data, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Clarence S. Stein Influence in Swedish Town Planning (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Swedish Housing Policy (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - "New Towns: Humane Oases" by Eckardt, November 27, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Cottons Papers (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Clarence S. Stein Research Proposal: Visual Aspects of "Community" (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Clarence S. Stein Links - Final, May 26, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Footnote Research, Ecole De Beaux Arts, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Letters, Papers Introduction (Second Draft), November 1990 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Miscellaneous Footnotes and Chronology (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Correspondences (1931), May 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Correspondences (1932-1933) (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Stein Letters (1934-1935) (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Introduction and Links, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Stein Letters (1936-1939) (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Footnote Corrections - Correspondence (1940-1941) (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Stein Letters (October 1941 - April 1943), May 15, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Stein Letters (Mid-1944 - 1949), May 17, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Final Footnote Revisions - Stein Letters (1943-1945), May 16, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Manuscript of Correspondence and Essays (1903-1919), Footnote Drafts, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Notes on 12/10/1948 Letters (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Clarence S. Stein Letters - Penultimate Draft, July 16, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; Notes, Correspondence, and Drafts (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; Notes, Correspondence, and Drafts (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Washington, DC, 1950-1951 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; JAPA Article, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - "Clarence Stein and the Greenbelt Towns: Settling for Less" by Parsons; JAPA Article Illustrations, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Shaping the Regional City, November 1990 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; SACRH Paper and Response, October 1989 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; National Archive, Research (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; National Archive, Research (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; National Archive, Research (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; Figures (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - "The Planning of the Town of Norris" prepared by Augur (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "Shaping the Regional City: 1950-1990" by Parsons; Correspondence and Articles (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Greenbelt: Historic District Study, February 1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Map of Baltimore, MD (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Howard County, MD The 1990 General Plan at a Glance (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Howard County News Articles, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Federal Employment and Federal Facilities, September 1982 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Clarence S. Stein Funding Proposals (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Clarence S. Stein Articles (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - The Writings of Clarence S. Stein Galleries/Illustrations (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Paper Drafts by Parsons (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Paper Drafts by Parsons (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Clarence S. Stein - New Towns in Great Britain (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Tyrone, New Mexico Files (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Dawson, New Mexico Files (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Silver City Museum - Tyrone, Dawson Material (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Tyrone Correspondence, Notes (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Paper Proposal - Clarence S. Stein and Tyrone, New Mexico, October 1997 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Tyrone Notes, 1995-1998 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Tyrone Photos, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Townsites Housing and Buildings, Tyrone (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Tyrone, New Mexico Footnote Data (1912) (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Tyrone and Dawson, New Mexico Prints (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Silver City Tour (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Tyrone, New Mexico Maps and Aerials (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - "British and American Community Design: Clarence Stein's Manhattan Transfer, 1924-74" (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings Final Manuscript, August 1996 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings Final Manuscript, August 1996 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings Final Manuscript, August 1996 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Community Architect: Selected Letters, Sketches, and Unpublished Writings Final Manuscript, August 1996 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Clarence S. Stein Defense Housing Illustration (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Clarence S. Stein - Early Education, New York, and Paris Photos (1890-1911) (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Transcript of Interview with Aline M. Stein, September 28, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Principals & Practice of Urban Planning, Chapter 10: Education Services and Cultural Programs by Parsons and Davis. Notes, Data, and Manuscripts, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Sunnyside Gardens Community Constitution, December 12, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Clarence Stein, RPAA Files (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Clarence Stein Correpondence, Articles, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Drafts and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Drafts and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Drafts and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Drafts and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Stein Drafts and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Cornell History
    - "The History of Campus Planning at Cornell", typed, bound copy, January 1952 (Box 1)
    - "The Quad on the Hill: An Account of the First Building at Cornell", reprint from Journal of the Society of Architectural Historians, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Cornell Campus: Index, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      handwritten on individual index cards
    - The Cornell Campus: Author's first proof plus copy of typewritten index, March 7, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Cornell Campus: List of illustrations, Author's second proof, April 12, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Cornell Campus: Photograph copies, many stamped "Collection of Regional History, University Archives", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Cornell Campus: Typed copy of front matter, contents, and list of illustrations, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Cornell Campus: Printer's proof, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The Cornell Campus: List of illustrations, introduction, title page, June 17, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, notes, and clippings found inside Parsons' copy of The Cornell Campus, 1969-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Cornell Campus, 1968 book with Parsons' annotations for possible second edition, 1989 (Box 1)
    - The Cornell Campus: Introduction and acknowledgments, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 10: The Expansion Begins, June 19, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 6: The Campus & the Community: 1868, June 20, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 1: The Founders and a Prophesy, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 2: Upon the Hill, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 4: Mr. Ruskin Would Be Pleased, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 5: An Un-Sectarian Chapel, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 1: The Founders and a Prophesy, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 2: Upon the Hill, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 3: A Quadrangle of Stone, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 4: "Mr. Ruskin Would Be Pleased...", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 5: An Un-Sectarian Chapel, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 6: The Campus & the Community: 1868-1880, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 7: Cottages and Villas, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 8: The Elegant Eighties, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 9: Where the Great Library Will Stand, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 10: The Expansion Begins, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 11: The Nineties Under Schurman, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 12: Campus Plans and Castle Dreams, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 13: White's Dreams Come True, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 14: Three Times Cornell, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - The Cornell Campus: List of illustrations, introduction, title page, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 1: The Founders and a Prophecy, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 2: "Upon the Hill", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 3: A Quadrangle of Stone, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 4: "Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased...", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 5: An Unsectarian Chapel, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 6: The Campus and the Community, 1868 - 1880, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 7: Cottages and Villas, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 8: The Elegant Eighties, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 9: Where the Great Library Will Stand, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 10: The Nineties Under Schurman, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 11: Expansion Begins, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 12: Campus Plans and Castle Dreams, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 13: White's Dream Come True, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 14: Two Times Cornell, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - The Cornell Campus:Documents, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - The Cornell Campus: Acknowledgments, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - The Cornell Campus: Credits for illustrations, and note, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - The Cornell Campus: Index, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - The Cornell Campus, A History of Its Planning and Development: Proof form, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - The Cornell Campus: Title page,contents, list of illustrations, introduction, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 1: The Founders and a Prophecy, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 2: Upon the Hill, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 3: A Quadrangle of Stone, c. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 4: "Mr. Ruskin Would Be Pleased", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 5: An Un-Sectarian Chapel, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 6: The Campus & the Community, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 7: Cottages and Villas, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 8: The Elegant Eighties, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 9: Where the Great Library Will Stand, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 10: The Ninetys Under Schurman, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 11: Expansion Begins, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 12: Campus Plans & Campus Dreams, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 13: White's Dream Cones True, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - The Cornell Campus,Chapter 14: Two Times Cornell, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - The Cornell Campus: Acknowledgments, ca. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - "Busways in New Towns", 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Education and the State, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Norris Tennessee Files, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - "The Regional Planning Ideas of the RPAA, 1925-1965", 1995 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - History of Cornell - McGraw Tower Talk, 1989-1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - "Social Facilities for Large-scale Housing Developments" by Burnham Kelly, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - "Los Angeles Landmarks: The Top Dozen" The Los Angeles Times, February 19, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Figures & Objects by Jason Seley, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - The Civilization of Llhuros, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - "The Cape Cod Cottage" Design Analysis, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - New Towns Conferences and Writing, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - "Canadian Municipal Land Acquisition and Development Control" by Parsons, November 1972 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - "The Role of Support in the Growth of Planning Education in the United States" by Parsons, Jones, Riordan, May 5, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - "A Draft Proposal for the Development of Procedures for the Photogrammetric Mapping of Historical Environments" by Jones and McNair, May 1, 1974 - December 31, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Ebenezer Howard and the Garden City by Richert, Spring 1998 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - "Self-Study of the Department of Sociology and Anthropology for the Graduate Community Planning Program", March 5, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Proposal to the National Science Foundation, December 30, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - "Urban Renewal - The American Frontier" Winston Lecture, November 12, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Environmental Health Planning Training Grant - by Jones, 1975-1978 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - The Increasing Importance of the Life Cycle Costing Approach to Facility Construction' by Ingwersen, April 19, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Chapters 7-14: The Cornell Campus, The History of the Formative Years, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Cornell Campus Planning: 1920s Building Notes and Scenes, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Chapters 4, 9, 10, 11, 12: The Cornell Campus, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Chapter 7: Cornell: The Cornell Campus, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Cornell History Talk, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Chapter 8: The Last of the Victorians; The Cornell Campus, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Chapter 10: The Campus Perceived - A History of the Formative Years., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Chapter 11: The Campus Perceived - A History of the Formative Years., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Chapter 1: The Campus Perceived - A History of the Formative Years., 1965 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Slide lists and inventory for Cornell Campus Book, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Notes and Publicity for Cornell Campus Book, 1964-1968 (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Citizen Committee on Housing - Ithaca, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - US census of Housing:1960 - Ithaca, NY, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Before Cayuga, prepared by CR Roseberry, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Soil Survey - Tompkins County, New York, prepared by US Department of Agriculture, July 1965 (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Urban Renewal Workable Program - Ithaca, NY, 1955-1966 (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Ithaca - General Material, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - "Site Studies - New City Hall", prepared by Ithaca Planning Board, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Cayuga Lake Photos, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - "Plan for Downtown Ithaca" prepared by Ithaca Planning Board, February 5, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Sketches, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Housing Code of the City of Ithaca, NY, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Geology 101 Laboratory Manual, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University - campus Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - University Change and Unrest - Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Campus Unrest, Jan 1968 - Dec 1969 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - The University and Urban Change - Outlines, Miscellaneous Notes, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 10a)
    - The University and Urban Change - Outlines, Miscellaneous Notes, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 10b)
    - Famous Town Planners III - L'Enfant, prepared by Elbert Peets, July 1928 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - National Urban Policy Articles/Clips, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Regional Development Planning, prepared by Barclay Jones, October 1971 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Urban Policy Legislation Press Releases, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University Planning, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Community Assistance for Environmental Impact Assessment Review Under SEQR, July 1, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Chemung Valley Study for Higher Education - Complete Set, July 1968 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Public Land Acquisition for New Communities and the Control of Urban Growth: Alternative Strategies, prepared by KC Parsons, June 1972 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Education Services and Cultural Programs, by Parsons and Davis, undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - University District Renewal, Chicago, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 20a)
    - University District Renewal, Chicago, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 20b)
    - Columbia University Campus, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Gaming Techniques to Land Use, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 22a)
    - Gaming Techniques to Land Use, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 22b)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 5: The Cornell Community (draft 4), April 7, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 4: Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased (draft 4), March 10, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 3: Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased (draft 2), November 1963 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - The Cornell Campus: pages from Chapter 5, undated (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 6: Where the Great Library Will Stand (draft 4), April 29, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - The Cornell Campus notes, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 11: Expansion Begins (draft), undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 5: An Un-Sectarian Chapel (draft), undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 6: Where the Great Library Will Stand (draft 2), April 29, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 8 Notes, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 4: Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased (draft 6), April 25, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 4: Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased (draft 7), May 26, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 8: The Last Victorians (draft) with notes, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 5: An Un-Sectarian Chapel (draft), 1964 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 6: The Campus & The Community (draft 5), May 28, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 7 Notes, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 4 Notes, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 9: Where the Great Library Will Stand (draft 3), May 30, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - The Cornell Campus: Loose Draft Pages, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 4: Mr. Ruskin Would be Pleased, May 27, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 3: A Quadrangle of Stone (draft 3), April 25, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 1: The Builder - The Gentleman Scholar and a Prophesy (draft), 1964 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 2: Upon the Hill (draft), October 17, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 5: The Campus & The Community, 1968-1885, undated (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 6 Notes, undated (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 3: Mr. Ruskin Would Be Pleased (draft 3), January 3, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 1: The Builder - The Gentleman Scholar and a Prophesy (draft, rewritten after Jacobs comments), April 1964 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 1: The Builder - The Prophet, the Builder, and the Gentleman Scholar (draft 3), January 17, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 2: Upon the Hill (draft, rewritten after Jacobs comments), 1964 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - The Cornell Campus: Chapter 1: The Builder - The Prophet, the Builder, and the Gentleman Scholar; Chapter 2: Upon the Hill (draft 5), April 17-25, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - The Cornell Campus Notes, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Historical Campus Planning at Cornell - Final Illustration Lists, June 1, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - The Cornell Campus, Chapter 1, January 16, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Campus Planning at Cornell (1865-1965) Lecture, undated (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - The Cornell Campus, Chapter 2: 'The Quad on the Hill' (4th draft), 1964 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - The Cornell Campus, Chapter 2: 'The Quad on the Hill' (3rd draft), 1964 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - The Cornell Campus, Chapter 1: The Prophet, The Builder, and the Architect (draft 4), January 1964 (Box 79, Folder 32)